# **SARAH THIELSEN**

**(**587) 896-0692

skthielsen@gmail.com

🔀 Calgary, AB

## **ABOUT ME**

As a creative and collaborative individual beginning my career in UX Design, I specialize in User Interface design, Marketing, and Information Architecture. With a keen eye for detail and a deep understanding of user behaviour, I am able to design interfaces that are not only visually appealing but also user-friendly.

# **EDUCATION**

# CareerFoundry University of Calgary

Certification in UX Design Bachelor of Nursing

GPA 3.8

2022-2023 2017-2021

# **EXPERIENCE**

## Fitness Advisor (Sales)

Aug 2022- Present

Goodlife Fitness

- Provided exceptional customer service and support to members to help them achieve their fitness goals.
- Conducted personalized fitness consultations with members, assessing their fitness levels, discussing their fitness goals, and developing customized fitness plans.
- Built and maintained strong relationships with members and took responsibility to ensure their fitness goals were being met days, weeks, and months later.
- Consistently met and exceeded monthly membership and revenue goals, contributing to the success of the fitness center.

#### Health Care Aid

Sept 2019 - Aug 2022

Erin Novakowski

- Offer social support by transporting client to events and activities, in addition to medical appointments and shopping trips
- Assist client with daily living needs, including bathing and personal grooming, to maintain self-esteem and general wellness.
- Built strong relationship with client to deliver emotional support and companionship.

# **SKILLS**

Resourceful Problem Solver

Strong Communication &

Interpersonal Skills

Curious & Empathetic

Self Motivated

Detail Oriented & Organized

# **TOOLS**

### Digital Marketing & Design

Adobe Suite

Microsoft Office Suite

Google Office Suite

Figma

Squarespace

Canva

Sketch

### Front-End Languages

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript